We're not fighting;
we're just...
(Leonard:)having a conversation.
(Wil:)All right.
(Wil:)We're listening
to a really fun conversation
(Wil:)between my costar
from Serial Ape-ist 2
and her fiancé,
who doesn't believe
(Wil:)women should have dreams.
(Leonard:)Give me back that juice.
(Penny:)What is the harm
if I audition?
(Leonard:)Well, what if you get it?
(Penny:)I don't know, I make a movie,
(Penny:)become rich and famous,
(Penny:)win an Oscar, a Golden Globe
(Penny:)and live an incredibly
wonderful life.
(Leonard:)From a Kevin Smith movie?
KEVIN:
Oh, I'm hanging up now.
(Wil:)Don't you listen
to him, buddy.
(Wil:)You're awesome.
(Wil:)You're one of the greatest
directors of our time.
(Caller:)I don't have
a part for you, Wheaton.
(Wil:)And that was Kevin Smith.
(Wil:)Thanks a lot.
(Leonard:)I'm just trying to protect you.
(Leonard:)How many times did I see you
get your heart broken
(Leonard:)trying to make it
as an actress?
(Penny:)Okay, instead of protecting me,
why don't you try
(Penny:)being excited when
something good happens?